I'm Jake O'Neill creator of animagraphs
我是杰克·奥尼尔动画的创造者
and this is how a World War II submarine works
这就是二战潜艇的工作原理
we've built a generalized teaching model from the era
我们建立了一个通用的教学模式从那个时代开始
for those interested
对于那些感兴趣的人
our source
我们的来源
inspiration comes from Gato and Belayo class boats
灵感来自Gato和Belayo级船
the submarine consists of a reinforced tube
潜艇由一根加强管组成
called the pressure hole
叫做压力孔
running the length of the ship
运行船的长度
which houses all personnel and sensitive machinery
容纳所有人员和敏感机械
this inner hull
这个内壳
is divided into eight
被分成八个
individually watertight compartments
单独水密隔间
which are separated by reinforced structural barriers
被加固的结构屏障隔开
called bulkheads
称为舱壁
special pressure rated doors separate
特殊额定压力门分开
and isolate these bulkheads
隔离这些舱壁
which we'll examine later
我们稍后会检查。
an additional watertight cylinder above the hole
孔上方的附加水密圆柱体
forms the conning tower
形成了指挥塔
wrapped around this core
围绕着这个核心
there's an outer hole which houses tanks for fuel
外面有个洞用来装燃料
ballast water air
压载水空气
and other essential liquids and gases
以及其他必需的液体和气体
a hollow superstructure extends
中空的上层建筑延伸
along the top of the boat
沿着船的顶部
from the main deck
从主甲板
with limber holes so water can flood or drain as needed
带有弹性孔，以便水可以根据需要淹没或排出
now let's get into the details
现在让我们进入细节
starting at the front or bow of the ship
从船的前部或船头开始
there's a large buoyancy tank
有一个大浮箱
that's part of the diving system
那是潜水系统的一部分
shutters on both sides cover six forward torpedo tubes
两边的百叶窗覆盖了六个前鱼雷发射管
the anchor is perched here connected by 600
锚栖息在这里由600连接
feet of chain
链条英尺
the anchor can free fall when released
锚释放时可以自由落体
a motorized device called a wildcat
一种叫做野猫的机动装置
hauls the chain back up
把链条拉回来
storing it in a special chain locker near the bow
存放在船头附近一个特殊的锁链储物柜里
the bow planes are also nearby
船头飞机也在附近
a hydraulic ram drives a shaft to tilt the planes
液压柱塞驱动轴使飞机倾斜
allowing the submarine to
允许潜艇
in a way fly through the water
在某种程度上飞过水面
when submerged
淹没时
the planes fold up while surfaced
飞机在浮出水面时折叠起来
since they're no longer needed
因为他们不再需要了
and to protect them from rough seas
保护它们免受汹涌海洋的伤害
from here we can see the forward torpedo room
从这里我们可以看到前方鱼雷室
there are 16 torpedoes here
这里有16枚鱼雷
with six in the tubes ready to fire
管子里有六个准备开火
and 10 reloads stored in the compartment
和10个储存在隔间里的重装
they're 20 plus feet long and 21 inches in diameter
它们长20多英尺直径21英寸
weighing about 3,000 pounds each
每个重约3000磅
between the tubes there's the Gyro Angle Setter
管子之间是陀螺仪角度设置器
which continuously updates the angle setting
它不断更新角度设置
inside the torpedoes
在鱼雷里面
for firing at a different angle or course
以不同的角度或路线射击
than the submarine itself
而不是潜艇本身
resulting in a curved shot
导致弯曲的镜头
these analog computers are one of many such devices
这些模拟计算机是许多这样的设备之一
on board which we'll examine in more detail
在船上，我们将更详细地检查
as we encounter them
当我们遇到他们时
the torpedoes themselves are expensive
鱼雷本身很贵
technically advanced machines
技术先进的机器
the gyro angle setting from the computer is translated
来自计算机的陀螺仪角度设置被翻译
through a rotating shaft on the tube
通过管子上的转轴
to set the torpedoes inner gyro
设置鱼雷内陀螺仪
rods extend from the gyro rearward to rudder
杆从陀螺仪向后延伸到方向舵
every torpedo has its own adjusted setting
每个鱼雷都有自己的调整设置
based on its location in the submarine
根据它在潜艇里的位置
torpedo depth and speed are set by hand
鱼雷深度和速度由人工设定
from controls on the side of the tube
从管子侧面的控件
the gyro angle can also be set by hand if needed
如果需要，陀螺仪角度也可以手动设置
there are six movable bunks suspended from the ceiling
天花板上悬挂着六个可移动的床铺
but this compartment could accommodate up to 15 beds
但这个隔间最多可容纳15张床
there's a crew's head or toilet here
这里有一个船员的头或厕所
and a shower that's mostly used by officers
还有军官常用的淋浴间
a hatch overhead provides access to the escape trunk
头顶的舱门提供了逃生通道
which in turn leads to the bridge
这反过来又通向桥
the escape trunk can be individually sealed
逃生箱可以单独密封
and either flooded or drained
要么被淹没，要么被抽干
flooding may be necessary
洪水可能是必要的
to equalize inside and outside pressure
平衡内外压力
for safe human passage in adverse conditions
在恶劣条件下的安全通行
the underwater log is attached to the port side hole
水下原木附在左舷孔上
with a rod that extends 3 feet beyond the outer hole
用一根延伸到外孔3英尺的棍子
the rod has openings at the tip
杆子尖端有开口
through which seawater flows
海水流经的地方
to measure pressure differences
测量压力差异
and thereby derive speed and distance traveled
从而推导出行驶的速度和距离
heading aft or rearward
向后或向后航行
we pass through a bulkhead with its watertight door
我们穿过有水密门的舱壁
we've now moved into officers quarters
我们现在搬进了军官宿舍
there's a small pantry here
这里有个小储藏室
for serving food to officers
为军官提供食物
though
虽然
only coffee and toast are actually prepared here
这里其实只准备了咖啡和吐司
with food itself coming from the cruise galley
食物本身来自游轮厨房
the adjacent officers'wardroom serves as a mess hall
邻近的军官室用作食堂
recreation room workspace and meeting room
娱乐室工作区和会议室
there are four bunks at the other side
另一边有四个铺位
with an additional six bunks down the hall
走廊另加六个床位
the rooms are partitioned with textile curtains
房间用纺织窗帘隔开
the captain's room is separate from the rest
船长的房间和其他房间是分开的
with redundant course indicator and depth gauges
带有冗余的航向指示器和深度计
mounted on the wall
挂在墙上
a writing desk
写字台
and wall mounted components
和壁挂式组件
for access to the ship's communication systems
进入飞船的通讯系统
there would be
会有
anywhere from six to eight officers on board
船上有6到8名军官
there's a small office at the end of the hall
大厅尽头有个小办公室
with a typewriter for record keeping
用打字机保存记录
from office to country
从办公室到国家
we pass through another bulkhead into the control room
我们通过另一个舱壁进入控制室
which is packed to the last square inch
包装到最后一平方英寸
with state of the art technology for its time
拥有当时最先进的技术
at the center
在中心
there's a dead reckoning tracer
有一个死亡推算追踪器
which takes input from the previously shown
它从前面显示的输入中获取输入
underwater log device
水下测井仪
and the nearby master compass
和附近的主指南针
to automatically move a pencil
自动移动铅笔
which draws the ship's course on a map or chart
在地图或海图上画出船的航线
underneath
下面
it has knobs to make adjustments
它有旋钮可以进行调整
or recalibrate the device when maps are swapped out
或在更换地图时重新校准设备
the Master Gyrocompass occupies a large case
罗盘大师占据了一个大箱子
underneath a central table
在中央桌子下面
with a shatterproof glass viewing port
带防碎玻璃观察口
it uses gyroscopic forces to find true north
它利用陀螺力来寻找真正的北方
instead of magnetic north
而不是磁北
magnetic compass
磁罗盘
accuracy
精度
can be negatively affected by other electrical
会受到其他电气的负面影响
or metal objects
或金属物体
including the ship's hull
包括船体
at the heart of the gyrocompass
在陀螺罗盘的中心
a spinning element sits suspended in a cup
一个旋转的元素悬浮在杯子里
partially filled with mercury
部分充满汞
this element's rotation is electrically driven
这个元件的旋转是电动的
the cup is part of a hollow metal sphere
杯子是中空金属球的一部分
that is itself suspended in mercury
它本身悬浮在水银中
encased by an outer supporting sphere
由外支撑球体包裹
the core apparatus is held and isolated from shocks
核心设备被保持并与冲击隔离
by a ring of soft springs
一圈柔软的弹簧
and flexible metal bumpers with felt tips
和带毡尖的柔性金属保险杠
which extend from an inner gimbal ring
从内万向节环延伸
through connection to an outer gimbal ring
通过连接到外部万向节环
the compass maintains its own specific orientation
指南针保持自己特定的方向
apart from the submarine's movement
除了潜艇的移动
the highly sensitive
高度敏感
spinning core
纺丝芯
maintains its relationship to Earth's gravity
维持它与地球引力的关系
allowing finite
允许有限
directional changes to be continuously tracked
持续跟踪方向变化
above this central table there's a bathy thermograph
在这张中央桌子的上方有一个恒温仪。
that charts water temperature at various depths
绘制不同深度的水温
on paper cards
在纸质卡片上
water temperature affects
水温影响
among other things sonar range and accuracy
声纳的范围和精度
including avoiding sonar detection from other vessels
包括避免其他船只的声纳探测
there's a fathometer
有一个测深仪
which displays the result of pings
显示ping的结果
to determine the depth of water below the keel
来确定龙骨下面的水深
there are repeating gauges for target bearing and range
目标方位和射程有重复的仪表
along the port side wall
沿左舷壁
which would be the left side of the submarine
也就是潜艇的左侧
looking towards the front
朝前看
there's the diving station
那是潜水站
with separate wheels
有单独的轮子
to control the previously shown bow
控制前面显示的弓
plane angle
平面角
and a similar plane at the stern
船尾还有一架类似的飞机
each wheel has its own water depth to keel gauge
每个轮子都有自己的水深到龙骨量规
plane angle indicator
平面角度指示器
an inclinometer
测斜仪
that works something like a construction level
这就像一个建筑水平
using an air bubble in a liquid
利用液体中的气泡
to track boat angle
跟踪船角度
with separate glass tubes
带有单独的玻璃管
for coarse and fine readings
用于粗略和精细读数
in the center there's a deep depth gauge
在中心有一个深度测量仪
and a barometer to measure internal air pressure
和一个气压计来测量内部气压
moving forward
前进
on this side there's the whole opening indicator panel
在这边有整个打开指示器面板
with status lights
带状态灯
which show red for open or green for closed
打开显示红色，关闭显示绿色
corresponding to the many vents
对应许多通风口
exhaust ports hatches and so on
排气口舱口等
through which seawater may enter
海水可以通过它进入
the boat is ready to dive when all lights are green
船准备下潜当所有的灯都是绿色的
even then some air is pumped into the boat
即使这样，也有一些空气被泵入船中
and the barometer gauge is checked
并且检查了气压计
to verify increased internal pressure
以验证增加的内部压力
ensuring water tightness
确保水密性
below that the main hydraulic controls
下面是主要的液压控制
which control vents
哪个控制通风口
valves and many other crucial hydraulic systems
阀门和许多其他关键的液压系统
at the back of this side
在这一边的后面
there's the trim manifold
这是修剪歧管
which is used to pump water from
它是用来抽水的
and to the sea
和大海
or between tanks
或坦克之间
on the opposite or starboard side of the control room
在控制室的对面或右舷
starting from the rear
从后面开始
we see the air manifolds and gauges
我们看到了空气歧管和仪表
this station manages air throughout the boat
这个气站管理着船上的空气
air is used in ballast tanks
压载舱使用空气
for firing torpedoes
发射鱼雷
to run many gauges and instruments on board
在船上运行许多仪表和仪器
for ventilation and breathing and so on
用于通风和呼吸等等
in front of that
在那前面
there's the gyrocompass control panel
这是罗盘控制面板
with metal twist knobs
带金属旋钮
indicator lights
指示灯
and gauges to oversee gyrocompass function
和仪表来监督陀螺罗盘的功能
and relay readings to various repeating gauges
并将读数继电器到各种重复仪表
at other locations
在其他地方
aboard the vessel
在船上
next to that there's a large switchboard
旁边有一个大的总机
to monitor
监视
and configure the many electrical systems on board
并配置船上的许多电气系统
and also indicate the status of machinery
并指出机器的状态
to other parts of the ship
到船的其他部分
at the front of the control room
在控制室的前面
there's an auxiliary steering station
有一个辅助转向站
the boat's main steering wheel is in the conning tower
船的主方向盘在指挥塔里
an auxiliary gyrocompass sits behind this wheel
辅助罗盘位于这个轮子后面
there are repeater gauges for the underwater log
水下日志有中继器仪表
compass
罗盘
rudder angle
舵角
and motor order telegraph
和电机订单电报
which is used
使用哪个
to send motor orders to other parts of the ship
将发动机订单发送到船的其他部分
there's a ladder here
这里有个梯子
which leads to a hatch on the main deck
通向主甲板的舱门
at the back of the control room
在控制室的后面
we see two large periscope well tubes
我们看到两个大的潜望镜井管
that pass completely through the control room
完全通过控制室
with various equipment control boxes attached
附有各种设备控制箱
near the ceiling there are three colored alarms
天花板附近有三个彩色警报器
green is the diving alarm
绿色是潜水报警器
whose alert meant sailors had
他的警报意味着水手们
10 seconds to get below decks
10秒到达甲板以下
secure hatches and begin the dive
打开舱门开始下潜
the yellow alarm is for general quarters
黄色警报器是一般宿舍用的
meaning sailors would race to battle stations
意味着水手们会奔向战斗岗位
and prepare for combat
并准备战斗
the red is the collision alarm
红色是碰撞警报
when this alarm sounded
当警报响起时
sailors closed all watertight doors
水手们关上了所有的水密门
among other protocols
在其他协议中
there's a ladder here
这里有个梯子
which takes us into the conning tower
带我们进入控制塔
the conning tower gets its name from the root word con
控制塔的名字来源于词根con
meaning to conduct or steer
意为指挥或引导
this is the main attack
这是主攻
and navigation center for the ship
和船的导航中心
at the center there are two periscopes
在中心有两个潜望镜
let's zoom out and get the full view
让我们缩小并获得完整的视图
periscopes extend upwards through periscope shears
潜望镜通过潜望镜剪刀向上延伸
which are visible at the exterior
从外部可以看到
when the boat is surfaced
当船浮出水面时
Max effective periscope depth is 65 feet
潜望镜最大有效深度65英尺
which the submarine can reach in an incredible
潜艇可以以难以置信的速度到达
35 seconds Wells extend from the shears
35秒后，井从剪刀延伸出来
all the way to the bottom of the pressure hole
一直到压力孔的底部
with rubber bump stops at the end of their travel
在旅行结束时有橡胶缓冲站
the forward scope
正向范围
is the observation or search periscope
是观察还是搜索潜望镜
it's shorter but thicker in circumference
它更短，但周长更厚
making it easier for the enemy to see
让敌人更容易看到
it has superior capabilities in low light conditions
它在弱光条件下具有卓越的能力
below the main viewport there's a radar installation
在主视口下方有一个雷达装置
the rear scope is the ATAK Periscope
后瞄准镜是ATAK潜望镜
it's much thinner profile makes it harder to spot
它的轮廓更薄更难辨认
it's also about 4 feet longer
它也长了大约4英尺
allowing deeper dive depth
允许更深的潜水深度
back in the conning tower
回到指挥塔
handles are unfolded to rotate the periscope
把手展开以旋转潜望镜
handles also twist
把手也会扭动
to control other available periscope features
控制其他可用的潜望镜功能
the attack scope has an optical range finder
攻击瞄准镜有光学测距仪
to determine distance to target
确定到目标的距离
with a supporting statometer
带支撑定位器
which helps derive target distance
这有助于推导目标距离
by comparing viewing angles top to bottom
通过从上到下比较视角
for objects with a known height
对于已知高度的物体
turning towards the starboard or right side of the ship
转向船的右舷或右侧
looking forward
向前看
there's an inclinometer
有一个倾角计
there's also indicator gauges
还有指示器
and controls for various types of onboard radar
和控制各种类型的机载雷达
in front of that
在那前面
there's the sonar control panel with gauges and knobs
这是声纳控制面板，带有仪表和旋钮
to remotely direct various sonar projectors
遥控各种声纳投影仪
visible sonar components include a rotating hydrophone
可见声纳组件包括旋转水听器
at the starboard side of the bridge
在桥的右舷
for standard sonar capability
标准声纳能力
and two retractable sonar projectors under the hole
和两个可伸缩的声纳投影仪在洞下
near the front of the boat
在船的前面
for supersonic sounds
对于超音速声音
that is sound that humans can't hear
那是人类听不见的声音
without the aid of equipment
没有设备的帮助
back in the conning tower
回到指挥塔
there's a ladder which leads outside
有一个梯子通向外面
to the lookout platform above
到上面的瞭望平台
the main steering station is at the forward wall
主转向站在前方的墙上
with a ship's main steering wheel
用船的主方向盘
and familiar gauges for speed and distance traveled
以及熟悉的速度和行驶距离的仪表
rudder angle compass repeater
舵角罗经中继器
and a motor order telegraph
和一个汽车订单电报
moving to the port side wall
移动到左舷侧壁
we see the torpedo firing panel
我们看到鱼雷发射面板
with status indicator lights
带状态指示灯
and firing switches for each tube
每个管子的点火开关
behind that the Torpedo Data computer
后面是鱼雷数据计算机
this is an analog computer weighing in at about 1500
这是一台模拟计算机，重约1500磅。
pounds instead of circuit boards and chips
磅而不是电路板和芯片
it uses electrically driven physical gears
它使用电动物理齿轮
wheels levers and so on
车轮杠杆等
to make complex trigonometry calculations
进行复杂的三角计算
for accurate torpedo
精确鱼雷
firing between the constantly moving submarine
在不断移动的潜艇之间开火
and targets at ranges up to 9000 yards
目标射程可达9000码
and angle shots up to 90 degrees right or left
和90度左右的角度拍摄
calculation results are sent to other systems on board
计算结果发送到船上的其他系统
against the back wall
靠着后墙
there's a dead reckoning tracer
有一个死亡推算追踪器
like the one found in the control room
就像在控制室发现的那个
let's head back down the ladder
让我们回到梯子上
at the rear of the control room
在控制室的后面
there's a separate radio room
有一个单独的无线电室
which is filled with communication equipment
里面装满了通讯设备
near the door there's a special cipher machine
门附近有一台特殊的密码机器
for receiving and transmitting coded messages
用于接收和发送编码消息
traveling aft or rearward
向后或向后行驶
through another pressure bulkhead
通过另一个压力舱壁
we enter the main crew areas
我们进入主船员区
where the ship's 60 to 70 crew members eat
船上60到70名船员在那里吃饭
sleep and congregate during off duty hours
下班时间睡觉和集合
all the food for the crew and officers
船员和军官的所有食物
is prepared in this small galley
是在这个小厨房里准备的
a large distinctive coffee urn or percolator
一个大的独特的咖啡瓮或渗滤壶
is at the open end of the galley
在厨房的开口端
for easy access to crew
便于接近船员
there's a floor hatch for food storage in the hold
货舱里有一个储存食物的舱口
the mess area has various tables
食堂区有各种桌子
with benches that double as storage chests
长椅兼作储物箱
apart from meals the crew could relax here
除了吃饭，船员们可以在这里放松
listen to the radio or play board or card games
听收音机或玩棋盘或纸牌游戏
there's a bookcase at one end
一端有个书架
and a drinking fountain over the sink
还有水槽上的饮水机
among various food storage and preparation compartments
在各种食物储存和准备室之间
a ladder near the back leads out to the main deck
后面的梯子通向主甲板
passing through the curtain at the end of the mess room
穿过餐厅尽头的窗帘
leads us into the crew's quarters
带我们进入船员的住处
there are 36 bunks for sleeping
有36个床铺睡觉
with individual storage bags
带单独的储物袋
suspended from the bunk rails
悬挂在铺位栏杆上
bunks were used in a shared rotation
床铺是共用的
between crew members
船员之间
with some sleeping while others were on duty
一些人在睡觉，而另一些人在值班
there's a dedicated ice cream storage freezer
有一个专用的冰淇淋储存冰箱
at the Starver side
在Starver一边
dangerous and stressful conditions aboard submarines
潜艇上的危险和紧张条件
meant
意味着
these sailors were afforded the best food in the Navy
这些水手得到了海军里最好的食物
to keep up morale
保持士气
at the back there are two restrooms
后面有两个洗手间
two showers
两次淋浴
and a washing machine
和洗衣机
we continue rearward
我们继续向后
heading through a pressure door into the engine room
穿过压力门进入机舱
four huge
四个巨大的
diesel engines provide power for the submarine
柴油发动机为潜艇提供动力
a few different types were common for the era
在那个时代有几种不同的类型很常见
I've chosen to feature the 10 cylinder
我选择了10缸
opposed piston model
对置活塞模型
each engine is individually rated for 1600 horsepower
每台发动机单独额定功率为1600马力
the engines extend between decks
引擎在甲板之间延伸
from the bottom to the top of the pressure hole
从压力孔底部到顶部
at the sides
在边上
they rotate opposite one another for balance
它们相对旋转以保持平衡
all are supercharged
全部增压
the air intake has an attached silencer
进气口有一个附加的消音器
to mitigate noise
减轻噪音
which would otherwise be deafening
否则会震耳欲聋
even so the running engines were so loud
即便如此，运转的引擎还是如此响亮
that operators used hand signals for communication
操作员使用手势进行通信
air intake
进气口
caused a strong breeze through the engine room
导致引擎室刮起一阵强风
air arrives at the engine room
空气到达机舱
from the main air induction valve
从主空气感应阀
just aft of the conning tower
就在指挥塔的尾部
its high position helped prevent flooding when surfaced
它的高位置有助于防止浮出水面时的洪水
engines are cooled with both a closed fresh water
发动机用封闭的淡水冷却
and an open seawater system
和开放的海水系统
seawater is sprayed into mufflers
海水喷到消声器里
to act as a spark arrester
充当火花避雷器
the engines exhaust out through side ports
引擎通过侧孔排气
beneath the bridge superstructure
桥下上层建筑
there's an additional smaller
还有一个更小的
7 cylinder auxiliary engine
7缸辅助发动机
at the bottom of the pressure hole
在压力孔的底部
there's a ladder at the back of the engine room
机舱后面有个梯子
for access to the main deck
进入主甲板
there are three special fuel ballast tanks with vents
有三个带通风口的特殊燃料压载舱
water flood valves
注水阀
and air blowers
和鼓风机
that can be used as part of the main ballast system
可以作为主压载系统的一部分
water fuel air
水燃料空气
or a combination of any of these
或这些中的任何一个的组合
can be distributed to these tanks as needed
可以根据需要分配给这些坦克
these are supplemented by four normal fuel tanks
这些由四个普通油箱补充
with valves for compensating seawater to enter
带有补偿海水进入的阀门
so the ship can maintain enough weight to submerge
这样船才能保持足够的重量下沉
saltwater is heavier than the submarine's fuel
海水比潜艇的燃料重
so seawater is pumped into the tank
所以海水被泵入水箱
but settles to the bottom as fuel is consumed
但随着燃料的消耗沉降到底部
heading further aft we enter the motor room
再往后走，我们进入机动室
the submarine uses a diesel electric setup
潜艇使用柴油电力装置
where each diesel engine
每个柴油发动机
has an attached electrical generator
有一个附加的发电机
power from these generators runs for electric motors
来自这些发电机的电力用于电动机
when submerged the diesel engines are shut off
当潜入水中时，柴油发动机就会关闭
and power from the motors comes from battery banks
电机的动力来自电池组
that take up a large portion of the submarine's
占据了潜艇的很大一部分
lower deck or hold area
下层甲板或货舱区
there are forward and aft battery compartments
有前后电池舱
with 126 battery cells in each compartment
每个隔间有126个电池
a single battery
单节电池
is about the size of an outdoor trash can
大约有一个户外垃圾桶那么大
these compartments have complex air and water systems
这些隔间有复杂的空气和水系统
for both ventilation and cooling
用于通风和冷却
when surfaced
浮出水面时
some of the generators
一些发电机
power is used to charge the batteries
电源用于为电池充电
now let's return to the motor room
现在让我们回到马达室
the ship has four electrical motors
这艘船有四个电动机
that operate best at high speeds
在高速下运行最好
motor shafts pass through a reduction gear
电机轴通过减速齿轮
since the propellers operate best at moderate
由于螺旋桨在中等条件下运行最佳
to slower speeds
速度变慢
noise from this reduction gear
这个减速装置发出的噪音
was the loudest sound produced underwater
是水下产生的最大声音
so much effort went into designing quieter gear
花了这么多精力设计更安静的齿轮
assemblies
装配体
from the reduction gear
从减速齿轮
two main propeller shafts extend outside the ship
两个主螺旋桨轴延伸到船外
on each side
在每一边
Max speeds on the surface
地表最高速度
using all available propulsion sources
使用所有可用的推进源
is 21 knots
是21节
while max submerged speed
当最大淹没速度
under battery power is 9 knots
电池电量不足9节
at max underwater speeds
以最大水下速度
the batteries only lasted about 30 minutes
电池只能持续大约30分钟
maximum underwater range is around 100 miles at 3 knots
最大水下航程约100英里时速3节
in practice most dives were short
实际上大多数潜水都很短
and any dive over
以及任何潜水
16 to 18 hours was considered dangerous
16到18小时被认为是危险的
located just above the motor room
位于机房的正上方
the maneuvering room
机动室
is the control center for this complex power plant
是这个复杂发电厂的控制中心
and propulsion system
和推进系统
the stand and its various levers control for example
例如，支架及其各种杠杆控制
electrical motor speed and rotation direction
电动机转速和旋转方向
they can remotely control the diesel engines
他们可以远程控制柴油机
there are gauges for propeller shaft speed
有螺旋桨轴速度的仪表
motor order telegraph repeater gauges
电机订单电报中继器仪表
and many smaller gauges to track the complex
和许多较小的仪表来跟踪建筑群
electrical circuitry throughout
整个电路
the system is highly flexible
系统高度灵活
for many combinations of both diesel
对于两种柴油的许多组合
engine and battery power
发动机和电池电源
for powering onboard systems and the propeller shafts
为机载系统和螺旋桨轴提供动力
there's also a fully functional metal working lathe
还有一个功能齐全的金属加工车床
at the starboard side
在右舷
the cubicle in the center is packed with components
中间的隔间堆满了组件
that link gauges
那个链接仪表
and levers to their functional counterparts
以及功能对应物的杠杆
there's a small
有一个小
engineers office at the back of the room
工程师办公室在房间后面
from here
从这里
we pass through the final pressure door into the aft
我们通过最后的压力门进入船尾
torpedo room
鱼雷室
there are eight torpedoes here
这里有八枚鱼雷
four in the tubes
管子里有四个
and four reloads on skids just behind
在后面的滑道上再装四次子弹
I've shown six bunks
我已经展示了六个铺位
though up to 15 could be deployed in this room
尽管这个房间里可以部署多达15个
there's another head here as well
这里还有一个头
as for the inside of the boat
至于船的内部
the only remaining compartment we haven't seen
我们唯一没见过的隔间
is the pump room
是泵房
which is beneath the control room
在控制室下面
it houses various air water and hydraulic pumps
它容纳各种空气水泵和液压泵
behind that and beneath the cruise galley and mess
在那后面，在游轮厨房和混乱的下面
is a storage space for food and ammunition
是储存食物和弹药的地方
submarines had various gun configurations
潜艇有各种火炮配置
our model features two
我们的模型有两个特点
40 millimeter guns for and aft of the conning tower
指挥塔后方的40毫米口径火炮
with a shorter range
射程更短
and one gun at the front for longer range targets
还有一把枪在前面瞄准远程目标
there are watertight
有防水的
pressure proof canisters mounted nearby with ammunition
装有弹药的耐压罐安装在附近
and replacement gun barrels
和更换枪管
all of these guns were used for anti aircraft
这些枪都是用来防空的
and some surface targets
和一些地表目标
the main deck has teak wood planks at the center
主甲板中央是柚木木板
painted black like the rest of the deck to camouflage
像甲板的其他部分一样涂成黑色以伪装
she could be completely invisible to human eyes
人类的眼睛完全看不见她
from overhead craft
从头顶上的飞行器
when submerged
淹没时
the raised portion at the center is the Fairwater
中间凸起的部分是费尔沃特
or sail which wraps around the conning tower cylinder
或者绕着控制塔圆柱体的帆
there are two target bearing transmitters
有两个目标方位发射机
which are optical devices to track enemy targets
用来追踪敌方目标的光学设备
there's a button to Mark the bearing
有一个按钮可以标记轴承
or angle of the target relative to the submarine
或目标相对于潜艇的角度
and automatically
并自动
send this information to the torpedo data computer
将此信息发送到鱼雷数据计算机
for use throughout the system
在整个系统中使用
there's a Searchlight
有个探照灯
and radar masts
和雷达桅杆
air
空气
is used in many critical submarine functions and tasks
用于许多关键的潜艇功能和任务
there are canisters that supply pressurized air
有供应加压空气的罐子
to eject torpedoes from tubes
从管子里发射鱼雷
other tanks supply air
其他储罐供气
for expelling water from ballast tanks
用于从压载舱中排出水
to resurface also called blowing the tanks
重新浮出水面也称为炸毁坦克
there's air supply for many components on board
船上的许多部件都有空气供应
and air for breathing when necessary
必要时呼吸空气
the ship had about
这艘船大约
15 hours of breathable oxygen at dive time
潜水时可呼吸15小时氧气
fresh air could be added from stores
可以从商店添加新鲜空气
but would increase internal boat pressure
但会增加船内压力
releasing emissions of any kind including air bubbles
释放任何种类的排放物，包括气泡
might be dangerous in close quarters with enemy craft
与敌机近距离接触可能会很危险
diving to dive
潜水
all engine and ventilation
所有发动机和通风
intake and exhaust ports are closed
进排气口关闭
ballasted tank vents are opened
有压载的油箱通风口打开
to allow air to escape and water to enter
让空气逸出让水进入
inducing a state of negative buoyancy
引起负浮力状态
the bow planes are rotated to guide the ship
船首平面旋转来引导船
into a dive
俯冲
driven by the ship's forward movement
由船的前进驱动
rotating stern planes
旋转尾翼飞机
adjust the dive angle
调整俯冲角度
once the desired depth is reached
一旦达到所需深度
some air is pumped back into ballast tanks to achieve
一些空气被抽回压载舱以实现
neutral buoyancy
中性浮力
water is also moved between tanks for a balanced trim
水也在水箱之间移动，以实现平衡
meaning the angle of the boat should be level
意思是船的角度应该是水平的
without excessive help from the planes
没有飞机的过度帮助
at depth
在深处
bow planes are now used to alter the ship's depth
船首平面现在被用来改变船的深度
doors individual
门个体
watertight compartments
水密舱
can serve to isolate damaged areas of the hull
可以用来隔离船体的受损区域
so the ship can remain afloat
这样船才能保持漂浮
even if one section is flooded
即使有一段被淹了
as such special doors
就像这样的特殊门
are designed to withstand high pressure conditions
设计用于承受高压条件
they're installed into the reinforced bulkheads
它们被安装在加固的舱壁上
there are sturdy
有坚固的
rotating levers at the edges of the door called dogs
门边缘的旋转杠杆叫做狗
with a couple turns of a central handle
有几个中央手柄
a worm gear actuates parts connected to individual dogs
蜗轮驱动连接到单个狗的零件
rotating these levers into place
将这些杠杆旋转到位
the inherent leverage in the system
系统中的固有杠杆
makes for a tight seal
使密封紧密
as the rubber door gasket
作为橡胶门垫圈
presses against an exposed metal part of the door frame
按压门框外露的金属部分
called the knife edge
叫做刀刃
these submarines are sea going works of art
这些潜艇是海上艺术品
and even with the detail I've shown
即使我展示了这些细节
there's so much more to them than I could cover here
他们比我在这里描述的要多得多
I'm in awe
我很敬畏
of the skilled folks who built these machines
制造这些机器的技术人员